http://www.barefootcentral.com/privacypolicy.aspx

Shopping Cart:
0
items (
$0.00
)
BFC The Magazine
AccessoriesApparelBarefoot BoomsBarefoot ShortsBarefoot SuitsBarefoot Training AidsBoats 4-SaleBoom AccessoriesCleanersCold Water GearDEALS!Drysuit AccessoriesDrysuitsExtended PylonsFAT SACsFlomo VestsGear & Ski BagsGift CertificateGlovesHandlesHeater ShirtsHelmetsJewelryJump SuitsMembershipsNeckbracesPre-Owned EquipmentRon ScarpaRopesShoe SkisSki & Wake VestsStickersSwimgearTower AccessoriesTowersVideosWetsuits
Home > Privacy Policy
BarefootCentral.com Privacy Policy
We strive to keep your personal information confidential. Please read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information:What information we collect:We collect the following personal information in order to process, fulfill and ship your order: your name and email address, your billing/shipping information including credit card number and shipping address, and your phone number.How the information is used:We use the information you provide to give you exceptional customer service, to fulfill requests for products, and to keep you up to date on backordered products you might pre-order.When we collect information:We only collect information about you when you purchase a product from BarefootCentral.com in order to process and ship your order.How we share your information:The information you give to us is not given or sold to any outside party except for the shipping companies we use to send your items. We only share your contact shipping address and phone number with the shipping company. We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.How we protect your personal information:The BarefootCentral.com website uses industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is required. To make purchases from the BarefootCentral.com store, you must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Netscape Navigator 3.0 or later, or Internet Explorer. This encryption technology protects your name, address, and credit card number during data transport. Some older browser versions and some firewalls do not permit communication through secure servers. In that case, you will be unable to purchase products. If you have already securely saved billing information to your account, you can still order securely using your saved information. However, if you submit new billing information through the non-SSL enabled server, it will not be encrypted. Access to your personal information. You always have access to the information we have about you by clicking on the link to your order in the confirmation e-mail you were sent when you ordered. If you did not retain a copy of this, you can request an invoice that we can email, fax or mail to you. If you would like to request a copy of an invoice, you can email us at:cg@barefootcentral.com. You can browse anonymously. When you browse the BarefootCentral.com website, you are able to do so anonymously. We do not collect personal information when you browse — not even your email address.Collecting information from children.BarefootCentral.com does not knowingly solicit personal information from children or send them requests for personal information.The BarefootCentral.com Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage you to review the privacy policy regularly for any changes. If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy polices or practices, we would like to know what they are so we can address them. Please contact us at:cg@barefootcentral.com.
Home | Login | View Cart | Become A Member | Contact Us | Size Chart | Warranty & Returns | Privacy Policy | BFC The Magazine
Copyright © BarefootCentral.com, All Rights Reserved.
All trademarks and brands are property of their respective owners.
